appia.com 2019-12-25

# Privacy Policy - Digital Turbine | Digital Turbine

Contact Us Get Started Today Start Monetizing Your Traffic 

  * 

Digital Turbine, Inc. and its subsidiaries (collectively, “Digital Turbine”, “We” or “Us”) recognize privacy as an important matter and have adopted this Privacy Policy to inform you of our data collection and use practices and confirm our commitment to keep your personal information secure.

Digital Turbine provides a broad mix of products and services through various channels. We provide products and services through websites we own or operate for our business partners (collectively, the “Digital Turbine Sites”). Certain products and services are primarily provided to our mobile operator and handset manufacturer partners, through software solutions of ours embedded in devices distributed by such business partners. Certain personal and non-personal information is collected and /or shared with us through products and services we provide we provide.

This Privacy Policy describes what user information we collect and store through the products and services we provide to our users and business partners, and how we use such information.

 **What We Collect**

As part of our products and services, We receive information in order to provision such services and to better service users and our business partners. Two types of data and information are collected by Us or shared with Us:

 **Non-personal Information** : which is non-identifying and non-identifiable information, without particular reference to the identity of the user from which such information was collected;

 **  and**

 **Personal Information** : which is individually identifiable information that identifies an individual, or may with reasonable effort identify an individual, either alone or in combination with other information, or may be of private or sensitive nature.  As part of our products and services, We may receive, collect and analyze personal information in order to provide services requested by or offered to our business partners, and to improve the features and usability of our products and services. Such personal information is acquired from either our business partners, the user’s mobile device, or directly from the user, and may include device usage information such as log information regarding the use of applications and device features, which applications have been downloaded, installed and uninstalled, wireless location, network traffic data, product and device-specific information and identifiers, service options the user chooses, mobile and device identifiers, and other similar information.

Our advertising partners may share with us information that describes how often users use their applications and information about events that occur within their application.

If you choose to access the Digital Turbine website, We may collect personal information which is shared with us (such as name, email address or other address you provide, and any other information you provide us when you contact us for support or provide feedback), to respond to inquiries and to allow login with email address and social media accounts.

 ** _Note regarding data practices in the EU_**

Digital Turbine is committed to comply with applicable legislation relating to its operation, including the General Data Protection Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council (“ **GDPR** “). Digital Turbine has implemented specific data practices regarding the provisions of its products and services in the EU, as described below:

For mobile devices activated in the EU, information collected through our products and services embedded in mobile devices activated in the EU is non-personal information. For such devices, the Digital Turbine products and services will replace any identifiers relating to a specific mobile device with a randomly generated identifier. This identifier cannot be used to identify a specific individual.

Based on the practices described above, and since Digital Turbine does not collect personal information from mobile devices activated in the EU, the GDPR does not apply to Digital Turbine’s operations relating to mobile devices in the EU.

 **Information Collected On our Websites**

When you use our websites, information may be collected through cookies and web beacons about your device and your visit including browsing activity as you interact with our sites; IP address; and information about your connection, including your device’s browser, operating system, platform type and Internet connection speed. We use this information for operational, performance measurement and other business purposes; We also may use this information to assess the effectiveness of our sites and to help you should you request help with navigation problems on these sites.

Visitors or subscribers of our services may provide contact information through our websites in connection with purchasing or content access inquiries; to find out more about Digital Turbine, and to be contacted by a Digital Turbine representative. We may use this information to respond to your request, and for business purposes such as marketing and research. We will not rent or sell this information to other companies.

 **How We Use Collected Information**

We use the information We collect for the purpose of providing our products and services as well as perform analysis to improve our products, services and technologies and those of our partners. The information also enables targeting capabilities that are most likely suited for our business partners and device users. In addition, We use the information to analyze the performance of advertising campaigns of our business partners and to provide them with performance reports.

 **Who We Share The Information With**

We do not share the data which We collect or which is shared with us, with third parties other than our business partners and users of our products and services that are strictly related with such data. Our business partners then may use the data for various purposes, such as targeting applications, advertisements or other content. We may also use some of the data We collect that can be publicly disclosed to create industry reports, analyses, and similar materials that We may use for sales, marketing or other business purposes.

Please note that there are some exceptions where We may be obligated to provide data to third parties such as regulatory authorities and law enforcement officials when We believe in good faith that the law requires such disclosure.

 **We respect ‘Do Not Track’ settings**

Users can indicate their privacy preferences through Limit Ad Tracking settings on iOS devices or Opt Out from Personalized Ads settings on Android devices. Whenever publishing partners pass us requests with the Do Not Track flag set, we do not retain any device-level data associated with the request.

 **Security**

 **We take industry-standard security measures that include physical, administrative, and technical safeguards that are designed to protect the personal information that We collect and maintain. Please be aware, however, that despite our efforts, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable and no method of data transmission can be guaranteed against any interception or other type of misuse.**

 **Contact Us For Any Questions or Concerns**

Please contact us at [privacy@digitalturbine.com](mailto:privacy@digitalturbine.com) with any questions about this privacy policy.

 **Changes To** **This Policy**

We may change our Privacy Policy from time to time. If We do, We will post such changes on our homepage.

Updated August 30, 2018.
